Mss.Rec.140 Mss.Rec.140
American Philosophical Society
Recordings in the Carrier language
1987-1988
Mss.Rec.140
American Philosophical Society
4.0 Tape(s)
4 audiocassettes (3 hr., 8 min.): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 1/4 track, stereo.
Prunet, Jean-Francois
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Presented by Jean-Francois Prunet in 1988 (Acc. 1988 2741re). This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
Related Archival Materials
A 56-page transcript of the recording is available in the Phillips Fund Collection (Mss.497.3.Am4).
Carrier language; Names, Carrier; Sound recordings
- Audio recordings
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Josephina Austin: 1-80, 1987-06-18; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:20:08; Austin, Josephina; Prunet, Jean-Francois
    Scope and Contents note
    The female researchers who can be heard on the recording are not identified in the recording's documentation.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Audiocassette) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Carrier language; Vancouver (B.C.)
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Josephina Austin: 81-116, 1987-06-19; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:47; Austin, Josephina; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 1-32, 1987-10-25; 01-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:26; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
    Burnaby (B.C.); Carrier language
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 33-91, 1987-11-01; 01-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:13:14; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 92-133, 1987-11-14; 01-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:08:24; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 134-161, 1988-01-17; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:30; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 162-215, 1988-01-24; 02-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:12:59; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 216-254, 1988-01-31; 02-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:09:12; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 255-276, 1988-01-31; 02-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:11; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 277-332, 1988-02-14; 02-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:13:48; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
    The word list on this program consists primarily of Carrier versions of English and French personal names.
    Burnaby (B.C.); Carrier language; Names, Carrier
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 333-377, 1988-02-20; 02-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:09:10; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
    The word list on this program consists of Carrier versions of English and French personal names.
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 378-392, 1988-02-21; 02-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:52; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 393-437, 1988-02-21; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:09:06; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 438-451, 1988-05-03; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:06; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 452-484, 1988-05-08; 03-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:05; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 485-508, 1988-05-26; 03-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:00; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 509-588, 1988-08-12; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:31:24; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois
    Carrier language; Tache (B.C.)
  - Carrier word and phrase list, Rose Pierre: 588-626, 1988-08-12; 04-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:15:38; Pierre, Rose; Prunet, Jean-Francois